🗷 sgchi@purdue.edu | 🏕 engineering.purdue.edu/people/seunggeun.chi.1 | 🖸 sgchi | 🛅 seunggeun-chi-963050153 | 🎓 Seunggeun Chi

Research Interests_

My research interests lie in Machine Learning and its applications to real-world problems. Representation Learning in Computer Vision problems is my primary study. My research also spans over Combinatorial Optimization problems which aim to extract rules by applying Reinforcement Learning.

Education

Purdue University West Lafayette, U.S.

Ph.D. STUDENT IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Aug. 2021 - current

• C-Design Lab, Advisor: Karthik Ramani

Seoul National University Seoul, S.Korea

M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING Mar. 2019 - Aug. 2021

• Optimization Lab, Advisor: ByungRo Moon

Seoul National University Seoul, S.Korea Mar. 2013 - Feb. 2019

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING • Computer Architecture Lab, Advisor: SangLyul Min

Publications & Patents

Conference Proceedings

- S. Chi*, H. Chi*, Q. Huang, K. Ramani. Skeleton-ODE: Learning Representation by Predicting the Future for Online Skeleton-based Action Recognition IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2023, submitted
- [C3] S. Chi*, H. Chi*, S. Chan, K. Ramani. Pose Relation Transformer: Refine Occlusions for Human Pose Estimation. IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA), 2023
- [C2] H. Chi, M. H. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, Q. Huang, K. Ramani. InfoGCN: Representation Learning for Human Skeleton-based Action Recognition. IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2022
- [C1] M. H. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, Y. Cha, B. R. Moon. Evolution-based Meta Reinforcement Learning for Portfolio Optimization. In proceedings of the 23rd The Genetic and Evolutionary Computation Conference (GECCO), 2021

Patent

• K.Ramani, H.Chi, S.Chi. Pose Relation Transformer And Refining Occlusions For Human Pose Estimation. U.S. Patent Application (MMB 1743-0299P)

Skills

Research and Development Stacks

Major Languages Python, C/C++, java, Verilog Machine Learning PyTorch, TensorFlow **Computer Vision** OpenCV, OpenGL

Web Languages Nginx, HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS

Database MySQL, SQLite

Other Tools and Skills

Other Langauges Shell Scripts(bszh, zsh), Matlab, R **Operating Systems** macOS, Linux Debian/Ubuntu, Windows

Text Editors & IDE Vim, VSCode, Eclipse

> Software SolidWorks, Catia, AutoCAD

> > VCS Git

Research & Project

Action Diffusion Model: Composing action from text-based input with Diffusion Model

C-Design Lab, Purdue Univ. Mar. 2023 -

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

• Aligned motion representation and text representation in the latent space.

- Developed latent diffusion model for effective diffusion process.
- Established novel action composition algorithm.

Skeleton-based action sequence generation with salient atomic actions

C-Design Lab, Purdue Univ.

Dec 2022 -

RESEARCH ASSISTANT Encode latent action trajectory with Neural ODE.

- · Extract the salient action frames of actions, and define atomic actions with the salient action frames.
- Apply diffusion model to generate continuous action sequences with atomic actions.

SEUNGGEUN CHI · CURRICULUM VITAE

Designing spatial-navigation on chrome-extension

ArchiLab, Seoul National Univ.

RESEARCH ASSISTANT Sep. 2018 - Dec. 2018

- · formulated malfunctioning cases and defined user-friendly environment
- Developed user-friendly navigation UI
- https://github.com/WICG/spatial-navigation

Academic Activities

Reviewer

- The IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2023
- Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2023

Education Outreach

- Gifted Education Research & Resource Institute (GER²I), 2022 Summer

Working Experience _____

SK Hynix Icheon, S.Korea

Intern Researcher Sep. 2017 - Dec. 2017

- · Designed an exclusive chip for testing 3D NAND flash architecture and verified the reliabilty of existing architectures
- Developed a module for predicting locality of data and tested it with real data

Korean National Police Agency

Dokdo, S.Korea

AUXILIARY POLICE

Dec. 2013 - Sep. 2015

Teaching Experience _____

Purdue University

ME 55300	Product and Process Design, 2023	Teachina Assistant
----------	----------------------------------	--------------------

Seoul National University

CS.4190.681A	Genetic Algorithm, 2019-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.4190.407	Algorithm, 2019-fall, 2020-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.M1522.407	Data Structure, 2019-spring, 2020-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.4190.308	Computer architecture, 2018-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.035.001	Digital Computer Concept and Practice , 2017-fall, 2018-fall	Teaching Assistant
PE.051.004	Volley ball, 2018-fall, 2019-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant

Honors & Awards

Competition of accelerating General-Purpose GPU sponsored by Intel

Manycore Programming Lab

1ST PLACE

Korea Ministry of Science and ICT

The National Scholarship for Science and Engineering

Mar 2019 Aug 2021

FULL SCHOLARSHIP

Mar. 2018 - Aug. 2021

Invited Talk

Yonsei University Seoul, S.Korea

GUEST LECTURER: REPRESENTATION LEARNING FOR HUMAN ACTION RECOGNITION AND GENERATION

Apr. 2023

Purdue Interdisciplinary Graduate Programs

West Lafayette

Presenter: Representation Learning for Human Skeleton-based Action Recognition

May. 2023